{
  "id": 501,
  "themeId": 5,
  "name": "Writing and Reading Singular/plural Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “tests”?",
      "options": [
        "Les tests",
        "Les testes",
        "Les textes",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les tests",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"chocolates\"?",
      "options": [
        "Les chocolats",
        "Les chocolatx",
        "Les chocolates",
        "Les chocolatex"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les chocolats",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “arms”?",
      "options": [
        "Vos bras",
        "Tes bras",
        "Les bras",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les bras",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “countries”?",
      "options": [
        "Les payes",
        "Les pays",
        "Les payent",
        "Les payies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les pays",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “birds”?",
      "options": [
        "Les oisox",
        "Les oises",
        "Les oiseaux",
        "Les oiseaus"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les oiseaux",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “kisses”?",
      "options": [
        "Les bisoux",
        "Les bisous",
        "Les bisoûs",
        "Les biso’us"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les bisous",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"lice\"?",
      "options": [
        "Les pouxes",
        "Les pouxs",
        "Les pous",
        "Les poux"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les pous",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"hair\"? (plural)",
      "options": [
        "Les chevaux",
        "Le cheveu",
        "Les cheveus",
        "Les cheveux"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les cheveux",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"plants\"?",
      "options": [
        "Les plants",
        "Les plantx",
        "Les plantes",
        "Les planteux"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les plantes",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"kids\" ?",
      "options": [
        "Les enfants",
        "Les enfantes",
        "Les enfantx",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les enfants",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}